Hi...we need to talk!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/ZixieChief/Zixie_Chief_I_Know_Stranger_Please.wav">I know stranger...please come with us.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/ZixieChief/Zixie_Chief_As_You_Can_See.wav">As you can see, we are a very peaceful tribe.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/ZixieChief/Zixie_Chief_For_Many_Years_We.wav">For many years we lived happily in our city, until
Great Council assigned us to protect the Medallion.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/ZixieChief/Zixie_Chief_Since_Then_Mentals_Troops.wav">Since then, Mental's troops have been
trying to locate Branchester, but without success.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/ZixieChief/Zixie_Chief_As_A_Matter_Of.wav">As a matter of fact, Mental's chances
of finding us, are a million to one.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/ZixieChief/Zixie_Chief_We_Are_Simply_Too.wav">We are simply too well hidden.
They will NEVER find us!
NEVER!
Warning! Intruder alert!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/ZixieChief/Zixie_Chief_Oh_My_God_They.wav">Oh my god, they found us!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Damn_They_Must_Have.wav">Damn, they must've followed me!