Huh?
Hmmm...
What the hell is that?
Whoooa!
Damn!
Aaaargh...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Phew_That_Was_Close.wav">Phew... that was close!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/ZixieChild/Zixie_Child_Sam_Sam_Saaam.wav">Sam, Sam, Saaaam, Saaaaaam!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/ZixieChild/Zixie_Child_Zumzum_Took_The_Medallion.wav">Zumzum took the medallion!
Ummm.... I know.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Zumzum_Took_The_Medallion.wav">Zumzum took the medallion! What now?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/ZixieChief/Zixie_Chief_Hehe_Dont_Worry_I.wav">Hehe... don't worry,
I know where he left. Follow us.