Hi, this is George B. Gnaar, reporting
live from Chi Fang City!
The citizens are gathered here
to celebrate their Majesty's birthday.
The ceremony will start any second,
with beautiful fireworks and entertainment programme.
There are even certain indicies,
that Prince Chan will perform his latest musical poem!
The citizens are eagerly awaiting the ceremony
to start and are truly honoured to be here.
Enjoy the event, LIVE, brought to you by
GNAAR NEWS NETWORK!
Gross!
Oh my god, that's AWFUL!
Now it's my turn!
Aaaargh!!!
Yeeehaaaw!
Ok, who's gonna go first, scumbags!
Time out!
I think we should wait for the old guy to leave!
I'll wait, if YOU wait!
Deal?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Quickly_Old_Man_Save.wav">Hurry old man, SAVE yourself!
Oh, for crying out loud...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Will_You_Go_Already.wav">WILL YOU GO ALREADY!
20 minutes later
Ok, guys, lets do it!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Netricsa/Netricsa_Prince_Chan_Is_Escaping.wav">Prince Chan is escaping!
Damn! What now?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Netricsa/Netricsa_I_Bet_He_Is.wav">I bet he is heading to Chan's Palace!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Netricsa/Netricsa_Lets_Go_There.wav">Let's go there!