Hmmm, I must be seeing things!!
Whadda hell?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Five_Million_Kleer_Drahmas.wav">Five million Kleer Drahmas?
IT'S A RIPOFF!
I think I need to have a little chat with the clerk!
Look, I don't have that kind of money!!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Gnaar/Gnaar_Then_You_Can_Go.wav">Then you can go back.
Hurry up!
But, I'm here to free the universe from Mental!!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/People/People_Hurry_Up_Man1.wav">Hurry up, man!
Yeah, just a second!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Gnaar/Gnaar_Sorry_No_Can_Do.wav">Sorry, no-can-do!
Pretty please!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/People/People_You_Are_Holding_Up.wav">Hey, you're holding up the line, come on!
I said, just a....What the hell!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Gnaar/Gnaar_No_Money_No_Pass.wav">No money, no pass. Easy!
Look, I really don't have time for this soooo...
RAISE THE RAMP AND HAND OVER THE CASH, BITCH!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Hehe_That_Felt_Good.wav">Hehhee, that felt good!