Oh, daddy, thank you for such a
beautiful celebration.
I wish this moment would
last forever...
Nooo! Stop him!
Princess, nooooooooo!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_It_Was_A_Perfect_Sunday.wav">It was a perfect Sunday morning,
but the air smelled of trouble.
Something told me this day wasn't
gonna be a good one.
One thing was clear -
they wanted to see ME.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_It_Had_Something_To.wav">Something about a missing princess...
it always is.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Suspicios_Faces_Stared_At.wav">Suspicious faces stared at me
wherever I looked...
..from every corner of the room....
... but, heck, I decided to play along.
Was it the groom?...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_The_Bloke_Looked_Suspicios.wav">The bloke looked suspicious just
standing there...quietly...almost happy.
Or...The King?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Hiding_His_True_Intentions.wav">Hiding his true intentions behind
huge shades
with a facial expression that looked
like it was carved into stone.
Or was it the Queen?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Nah_It_Definately_Was_Not.wav">Nah, it definitely wasn't the queen ... though I may
have to do some further investigation into her whereabouts.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Apparently_The_Princess_Had.wav">Apparently, the princess had been kidnapped,
and they wanted me to save her.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_They_Were_Also_Very.wav">They were also very clear about what
would happen if I refused to do it.
I decided to take the job.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Hell_If_The_Princess.wav">Hell, if the princess looked half as
good as her mother, who knows...
...the day could still have a happy ending...
if you know what I mean!