Gross!
I've come to take the princess!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Dragon/Dragon_Yes_Yes_It_Was.wav">Yes, yes, it was a mistake...
By all means, she's yours, you can take her.
Holy cow!
Umh, I... I changed my mind.
You can keep her!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Dragon/Dragon_Please_Take_Her_I.wav">Please, take her, I'll give you
anything you want!
Anything...?
No way dude, it's not gonna happen.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Its_Nothing_Personal.wav">It's nothing personal, you know...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Dragon/Dragon_Fine_We_Shall_Settle.wav">Fine... we shall settle this the old
way... but this time, LOSER wins...
...THAT!