Wow!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_My_Friends_There_Comes.wav">My friends, there comes a time
in life when one must take a stand...
... and that time is now.
And if you ever feel like giving up
just remember my words!
If we try now, we...
... shall never have a chance...
... to stand up...
...and defeat Mental!
So, be brave...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Enter_Those_Starships.wav">... enter those starships...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_That_Faith_Awaits_You.wav">... that fate awaits you!
Damn, it didn't work.
You go, I'll catch up with you.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_Still_Have_Some_Business.wav">Still have some business to do here...