This is George B. Gnaar, GNN LIVE.
We interrupt this program in order to
provide breaking news.
The Alliance maggots have penetrated our precious
shield and invaded the city.
However, there is no need to panic,
as our troops are well prepared.
See them crush the enemy into the oblivion...
...uhm, we'll probably see it later.
The important thing is to remain calm.
Mr. Mental assures you he'll deal
with this personnaly.
Oh my God, one of the alliance ships
is landing in the Arena!
It seems they are here to rescue that
hero wanabee we caught!
Dear Lord, these savages are
ruining everything.
We have reports that the enemy is deploying
the troops throughout the city.
And as you can see on your screens,
that Earthling managed to escape.
Don't worry, our Air defense troops are on standby,
and will shoot on sight.
We'll deliver more news as
soon as it happens.
George B. Gnaar,
Siriusopolis Arenas - LIVE.