Welcome to my humble home.
Yeah, well. I am here now!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Sam/Sam_We_Shall_Settle_This.wav">We'll settle this once and for all!
You need to know something first...
Yeah? WHAT?!!
Sam... I... am...
...your.... f...
Whatever...
Whadda hell ?!
Aw crap!
I knew it! I knew it!
I am gonna have to have serious talk
with Croteam one of these days...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy1_You_Are_Kidding_Me.wav">Oh, what,
you're kidding me, right?
Aww, this can't be the end!
Well, err...
Of course it's not, man!
I want to fight!!!
YEAH! Me too!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy2_Haha_This_Is_Funny.wav">Ha, ha, ha, this is funny!
It's NOT funny at all!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy3_They_Are_Not_Serious.wav">Hey, they aren't serious...
Are they?
Uh, y'know, they are just messing
with our minds, man...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy1_Maybe_Its_Really_The.wav">Hey, maybe it really is,
like, the end...
...or it's one of Croteam's bad jokes... again?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy5_Hey_Who_Is_Mental.wav">Hey guys, who is this
Mental anyway?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy4_Dont_Know_Nobody_Ever.wav">I don't know.
Nobody ever saw him.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy5_Does_He_Even_Exist.wav">Does he even exist, huh?
Yeah, I wonder how big he is...
Oh yeah, I would bet he's
even bigger than that Ugh-Zan...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy5_Yeah_He_Is_Probably.wav">Yeah, he is probably
bigger than planet Sirius...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy1_We_Will_Never_Know.wav">Oh, we will never know...
I WANNA fight!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy2_Haha_This_Is_Really.wav">Ha, ha, ha,
this is really funny, man!
No, it isn't!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy5_Guys_How_Many_Rockets.wav">Guys, listen... how many
rockets would it take to kill Mental?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy2_I_Guess_More_Than.wav">I guess more than a hundred.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy5_With_Hundred_Rockets_you.wav">With a hundred rockets you
couldn't even kill Bosses in other games.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy3_Stupid_Conversation_Cos_He.wav">Well, its a stupid conversation
'cos he ain't gonna appear.
Ha, ha, ha, this is
the greatest Boss in gaming history, man!
Hey mate, do you work for Croteam?
Listen guys, I gotta go to the toilet,
I hope he doesn't appear while I'm gone...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy3_He_Wont_Appear_At.wav">Like, man, he ain't gonna
appear at all, you understand that!?!
Oh, I'm sure he will.
No way man, look, you see,
this is the E. N. D...end...END!
Oooh-kay, I'm back, I would leave it
a little while, so...did he appear?
How does it look to you!
Did he appear? What do you think, huh?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy5_Hey_Maybe_We_Must.wav">You know while I was in toilet,
something popped up.
Maybe we've got to beat
the game on Serious difficulty?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/GuysAll_Yes_That_Must_Be.wav">Yes, that must be it!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy4_Damn_I_Could_Never.wav">Aww...damn,
I could never do that.
Oh man, it's not fair.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy6_Sorry_Guys_I_Have.wav">Err, I'm sorry gentlemen,
I have beaten the game on Serious,
but Mental didn't appear anyway.
I never seen a more
stupid ending to a game...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy2_Maybe_They_Are_Preparing.wav">Allright, well, maybe they are
preparing a sequel, man?
Maybe. It's, like, not the end!
Yeah, hey,
now the real fightin' begins!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/GuysAll_Pheeew_Yooohooo.wav">Pheeew, yoooohoooooooo,
GREAT!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Guys/Guy2_Lets_Kick_Some_Ass.wav">Let's kick some ass, man.
Awww, noooooo...
Here is the medallion!
Erm.. what!?
Nevermind,
let me take care of it.
Oh, what,
you're kidding me, right?
Whadda hell?!?
x@$^%!&*|!!
You can run,
but you cannot hide!
Can we just forget
about it?
I'm gonna shove that
Medallion up your a..!!!
You can't be serious?
Oh, yes I am!!!