<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode07/Sam/Sam_It_Is_The_Moment.wav">This is the moment that we've all been waiting for.
It's time to get rid of this Evil once
and for all! Are you ready?
Ready!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode07/Npc/Pilot_Acknowledged.wav"> Acknowledged!
Check!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode07/Npc/Pilot_Affirmative.wav">Affirmative!
Roger!
Rabbit!
2 hours later
Roger!
Ready!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode07/Sam/Sam_We_Are_Going_In.wav">We're going in... Follow me!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode07/Npc/Pilot_Oh_My_God_The.wav">Oh my God, the cannon is losing power!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode07/Wizards/Wizard2_Line01_He_Failed_And_I.wav">He failed! And I trusted you guys!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode07/Wizards/Wizard1_Line01_He_Is_Still_Very.wav">He's still very much alive, don't you think?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode07/Wizards/Wizard2_Line02_He_Is_All_Alone.wav">He is all alone deep inside enemy territory!
He has no chance at all!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode07/Wizards/Wizard1_Line02_Remember_Who_Are_You.wav">Remember who you are talking about. He is no
ordinary human. He is special.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode07/Wizards/Wizard2_Line03_So_When_I_Was.wav">So? When I was young they used to tell
me that I was special!!!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode07/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line01_Stop_This_Is_No.wav">Stop!!!
This is no time to argue, you can do that later.
IF there is going to be 'later'.
He is still our last hope. If he
fails we are all doomed!
I wonder what's happening to him now...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode07/Sam/Sam_Lets_Rock_And_Roll.wav">Lets rock and roll!
Yeeeeeeehaw!!!!!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode07/Sam/Sam_Oh_Boy_Oh_Boy.wav">Oh boy, oh boy, one more time!!
Crap!