<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard1_Line01_How_many_times.wav">How many times do I
have to tell you...he IS the one!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard2_Line01_If_that_is_our_last_hope.wav">If THAT is our last hope,
I don't believe we'll ever get rid of Mental.
C'mon, look at him! Would anyone sane believe that
this man can actually save the universe?!?!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard1_Line02_Well_It_Is_Written.wav">Well, it is written that a stranger
from a galaxy far, far away will come
and rescue us from the upcoming evil.
And the evil had already come...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard2_Line02_Was_Is_Also_Written.wav">Was it also written that he
will wear red sneakers?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard1_Line03_What_Do_You_Have.wav">What do you have against sneakers?!
You used to wear pink tights with yellow...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard2_Line03_Yes_Yes_And_You.wav">Yes, yes,... And you with
your ridiculous...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line02_Guys_Guys_Stop.wav">Guys, guys, STOP!!!!!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line03_Lets_not_forget.wav">Let's not forget why we are here.
We must contact him NOW.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line01_Concentrate_Boys.wav">Concentrate, boys.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Sam/Sam_You_Have_Exactly_5.wav">You have exactly 5 seconds to explain
what I'm doing here.
And 2 seconds have just passed...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line04_Please_mr_stone.wav">Please Mr.Stone, calm down.
We can help you in your quest.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line05_My_Name_Is.wav">My name is Rolanda and these are my
brothers, Jebediah and Rajiv.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Sam/Sam_I_Am_Sam_Serious.wav">I'm Sam. Serious Sam.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line06_We_Are_The_Sirian.wav">We are the Sirian Great Council and we are here
to show you the way how to stop Mental. Look...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line07_This_is_medallion.wav">This is the Medallion of Power...the only thing
that can make Mental weak and vulnerable.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line08_It_was_forged.wav">It was forged by a blind blacksmith Gromlin
and we, the wizards, threw a spell on it
following the instructions in our holy manual (revision 2).
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line09_It_was_split.wav">It was split into 5 pieces, and those
pieces were given to 5 different races...
Simbas from planet M'digbo...
...ChiChe from planet Chi Fang...
...Zixies from planet Magnor...
...Kleers from the planet Kleer...
...and Elvians from planet Ellenier!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard2_Line04_But_that_simply.wav">But that simply wasn't enough!
Pretty soon Mental had all the parts in its possession.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard1_Line04_Thankfully_those_pieces.wav">Thankfully, those pieces are indestructable,
so Mental can only guard them.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard2_Line05_When_All_Five_Pieces.wav">When all 5 pieces become joined again, medallion
will activate releasing it's power
and making Mental vulnerable.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line10_Your_task_is_to_go.wav">Your task is to go to planet M'digbo and
retrieve the first part of the Medallion!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard1_Line05_And_If_You_Bring.wav">And if you bring this piece back,
it could really mean you are...
...THE ONE!!!
The... one?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard1_Line06_The_One_Our_Holy.wav">The one that our holy manual,
(revision 2), keeps talking about.
The one who will
save the universe.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard2_Line06_Yeah_Right.wav">Yeah, right!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line11_Well_you_should_go.wav">Well, you should go now.
We'll get in touch with
you when you finish...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard2_Line07_If_You_finish.wav">IF you finish your mission!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line12_Shhh.wav">Shhhhhhh....
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode01/Sam/Sam_No_One_Is_Gonna.wav">No one's gonna believe this. Oh well...
AAAAAAAAARGH!
AAAAA!
CRAP!