<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line01_Unbelivable_He_Collected_All.wav">Unbelievable! He collected all five parts,
the medallion is complete!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Wizards/Wizard1_Line01_He_Did_It_I.wav">He did it. I knew it!
You owe me fifty.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Wizards/Wizard1_Line02_Nevermind_We_Now_Have.wav">We now have the medallion!
If we manage to get you to Sirius, Mental is doomed!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Sam/Sam_Manage_Is_There_A.wav">If we manage? ...Is there a problem
in getting to Sirius?!?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line02_Oh_Yeah_You_See.wav">Oh yeah... you see...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line03_Planet_Sirius_Is_Protected.wav">Planet Sirius is protected by an
impenetrable shield.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Wizards/Wizard2_Line01_Impenetrable_Even_To_Our.wav">Impenetrable even to our powers.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Wizards/Wizard1_Line04_You_Will_Need_Whole.wav">You'll need a whole Alliance Fleet
to attack Sirius!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Wizards/Wizard2_Line02_And_Mighty_Cannon_That.wav">And mighty cannon that can damage a shield.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Sam/Sam_Where_Can_I_Get.wav">Where can I get those?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Wizards/Wizard2_Line03_This_Is_Kronor_Small.wav">This is Kronor, small moon orbiting
around Sirius.
Huge military base is situated there which serves as
a Sirius defence post, as well as a prison facility.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Wizards/Wizard1_Line05_Thousands_Of_Alliance_Warriors.wav">Thousands of Alliance warriors are
imprisoned there.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Wizards/Wizard2_Line04_On_The_Colder_Side.wav">On the colder side of Kronor is another outpost,
containing the most powerful laser cannon in the galaxy.
If you locate the cannon, we can use it against Mental!
It should have enough power to damage the shield.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line04_Sam_You_Must_Free.wav">Sam, you must free the Alliance warriors.
Once you free them, they will capture enemy jet-fighters
and wait for you in orbit to activate the cannon!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode06/Sam/Sam_Consider_It_Done.wav">Consider it done.