Whadda..?!?
What is this!?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Wizards/Wizard1_Line01_Umm_Nothing_Next_Stop.wav">Nothing. Next stop: Kleer planet.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Sam/Sam_Kleer_Planet_You_Say.wav">Kleer planet you say...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Wizards/Wizard1_Line02_Yes_Kleer_Planet_Look.wav">Yes, Kleer planet...Look!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Wizards/Wizard1_Line03_What_Could_Be_Said.wav">What can be said about Kleer Planet..?
Volcanoes, rocks, some more rocks, more volcanoes.
And that would be the summary.
And lava. Lots of lava.
And Kleers ...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Wizards/Wizard2_Line01_Lots_You_See_Kleers.wav">Lots!... You see... Kleers were once keepers
of the medallion
before Mental dropped 10 billion gallons of
napalm on their planet and wiped them all out!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Wizards/Wizard2_Line02_Later_Mental_Raised_Them.wav">Later, Mental raised them from the ashes and
turned them into its most deadliest warriors!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Sam/Sam_And_The_Medallion_Piece.wav">And what about the medallion piece?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line01_Held_By_Evil_Wizard.wav">Held by the evil wizard Kleerofski!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Sam/Sam_Mmm_Sounds_Like_A.wav">Mmmm, sounds like a perfect place for a vacation...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Sam/Sam_Hah_I_Knew_I.wav">Hah, I knew I saw something!!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Wizards/Wizard1_Line04_No_You_Didnt.wav">No you didn't!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Wizards/Wizard1_Line05_Please_Use_The_Backdoor.wav">Please use the backdoor, it should
take you straight to planet Kleer
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Wizards/Wizard2_Line04_Bye_Bye.wav">Bye bye!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode04/Wizards/Wizard1_Line06_We_Should_Really_Get.wav">We should really get this thing fixed.