<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard1_Line01_I_Knew_It_You.wav">I knew it! You saw what he did to that
monstrous beast... he MUST be the one.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard2_Line01_He_Must_Be_The.wav">He must be the one, he must be the one...
...you said the same thing for that blondie guy
few years ago and look what happened!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard1_Line02_Oh_Him_But_It.wav">Oh, him... but it took him FOREVER
to even try!
This guy is different, I can feel it!
We should call him now!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line01_Yes_Yes_After_All.wav">Yes, yes, after all he managed to get
the first part of the medallion.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Sam/Sam_Isnt_It_Obvious_I.wav">Who's the one? Isn't it obvious... I AM!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard2_Line02_Dont_Be_So_Sure.wav">Don't be so sure...let's see how will you
manage the next one!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Sam/Sam_Bring_It_On.wav">Bring it on!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard1_Line03_Your_Next_Stop_Is.wav">Your next stop is Magnor!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line02_Magnor_Is_A_Gigantic.wav">Magnor is a gigantic planet. It consists of giant
forests, giant swamps, giant trees..
...giant plants, giant mushrooms...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Sam/Sam_Okay_Okay_I_Get.wav">Okay, okay, I get the point.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard1_Line04_From_Our_Latest_Intel.wav">From our latest intel data, it seems that the
medallion is still in possession of the Zixie tribe.
However, Mental doubled its efforts,
and decided to build an outpost in the swamps.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard2_Line03_Thousands_Of_Its_Minions.wav">Thousands of its minions are stationed
there in search of a missing piece.
Finding it should be
a matter of days.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line03_Mental_Also_Left_One.wav">Mental also left one of its
giant abominations to scout the area.
We don't know much about it,
so stay alert.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Sam/Sam_Dont_Worry_Say_Why.wav">Don't worry about it. Say... why don't you
just teleport me straight into the Zixie village?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard1_Line05_Well_You_See_We.wav">Well... you see... we don't
really know its exact location.
Probably the best place to start looking
would be around Mental's swamp base.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line04_This_Will_Be_A.wav">This will be a difficult task.
Painful, no doubt!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Sam/Sam_Yeah_It_Will_Be.wav">Yeah... it will be... for them!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard1_Line06_Good_Luck.wav">Good luck!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode02/Wizards/Wizard2_Line04_He_Will_Surely_Need.wav">He'll surely need it.