<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard1_Line01_See_Told_Ya.wav">See... Told ya!!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard2_Line01_I_Could_Have_Done.wav">Pih...I could have done it too!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard1_Line02_You_You_Couldnt_Even.wav">You?!? You couldn't even integrate
accelerated alpha voids into simple
polymorph submolecular quadristructures...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard2_Line02_Ha_Look_Who_Is.wav">Hah, look who's talking! YOU, on the other hand,
couldn't even...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line01_Enough_We_Have_No.wav">Enough! We have no time to lose.
Prince Chan's birthday party is in progress and we
must send Sam to Chi-Fang immediately!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Sam/Sam_That_Was_A_Piece.wav">That was a piece of cake, what's next!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard2_Line03_You_Did_Pretty_Good.wav">You did pretty good down there. Maybe you are
now ready for a real deal!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Sam/Sam_Yeah_And_What_Was.wav">Yeah? And what was that before?
Playing a videogame???
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line02_Nevermind_Lets_Get_It.wav">Nevermind. Let's get it on.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard1_Line03_The_Next_Part_Of.wav">The next part of the medallion is
on planet Chi-Fang.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard1_Line04_Chiche_The_Residents_Of.wav">ChiChe, the residents of Chi-Fang, will help
you, but there is nothing much they can do.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard1_Line05_They_Live_In_Constant.wav">They live in constant fear of being eaten by Prince Chan,
Mental's minion that is terrorizing the planet.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard1_Line06_And_What_Is_Most.wav">And what is most important and gruesome,
that damned thing ATE the medallion.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line03_Lets_Just_Hope_He.wav">Let's just hope he didn't go to the
toilet since then...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard2_Line04_Today_Is_His_Birthday.wav">Today is his birthday! There will be a big
ceremony on the main square. We made a plan!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard1_Line07_Yes_Here_Is_The.wav">Yes, here is the plan: You'll enter town...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard1_Line08_Arrive_At_Prince_Chans.wav">...arrive at Prince Chan's birthday party...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard1_Line09_Destroy_Him_And_His.wav">...destroy him and his servants...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard1_Line10_And_Take_The_Medallion.wav">...and take the medallion part.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard2_Line05_Simple_But_Effective.wav">Simple, but effective!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Sam/Sam_Could_We_Go_Through.wav">Could we go through it one more time...
I'm not sure I caught all of that...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Wizards/Wizard1_Line11_Okay_You_Will_Enter.wav">Oooookay... You'll enter town...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode03/Sam/Sam_Hey_Hey_Hey_Just.wav">Hey hey hey... just kidding.