<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line01_Boys_Thats_Enough_Is.wav">Boys, that's ENOUGH! Is that all
you can think about?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Wizards/Wizard1_Line01_But_Its_The_Galaxy.wav">But it's the
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Wizards/Wizard2_Line01_But_Its_The_Galaxy.wav">GALAXY CUP finals...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line02_Can_Anything_Be_More.wav">Can anything be more serious than saving the
universe?!? We must contact him now!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Sam/Sam_Who_Won_Who_Won.wav">Who won? WHO WON?
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Wizards/Wizard2_Line02_Is_That_All_You.wav">Is that all you can think about?!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Wizards/Wizard1_Line02_Yeah_What_Could_Be.wav">Yeah, what can be more serious than
saving the universe!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line03_Yeah_Right_Sam_You.wav">Yeah... right...
Sam, you must retrieve the last
part of the medallion!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line04_Ellenier_Home_Of_Elvians.wav">Ellenier... home of Elvians, a peaceful and noble race.
They successfully guarded the medallion...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line05_Until_Cecil_The_Dragon.wav">...until Cecil the Dragon came and took it.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Wizards/Wizard1_Line03_Your_Task_Is_Simple.wav">Your task is simple. Find Cecil...
get rid of him...
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Wizards/Wizard1_Line04_And_Take_The_Medallion.wav">... and take the medallion, finally proving
you are the ONE!
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Wizards/Wizard_Woman_Line06_You_Will_Start_At.wav">You will start at the top of the Heartbreak mountain.
There is a small village underneath.
We heard that dragon comes there once a
month to collect a fee.
<B sound="Content/SeriousSam2/Sounds/CutSequences/Episode05/Wizards/Wizard2_Line03_That_Will_Be_Your.wav">That will be your chance to meet Cecil...
head... to head!